Guide to the Cornell Club of Maryland records, [ca. 1940-2003]
Cornell Club of Maryland records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Club of Maryland records, [ca. 1940-2003]
41-6-3953
Cornell Club of Maryland.
3.3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes meeting minutes; subject files, including materials on activities and scholarships; newsletters; and files from the earlier separate Cornell Women's Club of Maryland.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Contains information from over 60 years about the Cornell Club of Maryland. Includes meeting minutes, information on clubs, activities and scholarships that the Club was involved in, including parties and alumni get-togethers. Also has lists of members throughout the years, and different descriptions of Cornell throughout the years.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Club of Maryland.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell Women's Club of Maryland.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Cayugan (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Men's clubs, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cornell Club Lists (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cornell Clubs general, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Merger, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cornell Club of Maryland, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cornell Club list, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Outstanding Club File, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Federation Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Penn Cornell lunch, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell Club fall dinner, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agenda Board of Gov. meeting, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Annual meeting, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Annual dinner business meeting, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cornell Trustee Nominitaions, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Dinner list, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cornell phone list, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fed awards submission, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sec. schools, pres. correspondence file (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Meeting exec board, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Federation Cornell (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cornell club of Maryland (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cornell clubs general file, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- History (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cornell club events and phone numbers (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Old membership files (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Changes in addresses, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Telephone committee, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cornell list of Maryland, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Board of Governor's meeting (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Cornell/sympathy, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Cornell fall dinner, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cornell club and Cayugan (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Mailing lists etc., 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Cornell Club financials (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Scholarship committee, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Cornell Club membership, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Navy dinner, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Smoker, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Penn Cornell lunch, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Annual Business meeting, May 19 1961 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Federation Board (Box 1, Folder 45)
- CCMD events, budgets etc. (Box 1, Folder 46)
- CCMD events and misc graphics (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Cornell federation/scholarship, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Smoker (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Club additions (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Meeting notices, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- CCCMD membership lists unedited (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Receipts, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Work Papers, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- University Placement Bulletins for Club (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Changes in addresses, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Current membership lists (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Federation of Cornell Men's club (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Communications from other officers (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Cayugans (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Cornell Fund (Box 2, Folder 10)
- General Membership, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence with Alumni Office of University, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Scholarship Committee (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Secondary Schools, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Scheduling of Events, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- University correspondence (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Thomas Nuttle Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Cornell Glee Club (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
- Fall Dinner, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Cornell Club (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Cornell Club Vice President By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Sustaining Members master list (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Cornell Votes (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Mailing Lists, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Incorporation and By-Laws, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Cornell Reservations (Box 2, Folder 28)
- "Letter from Cornell" (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Routine Business Matters (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Correspondence with other Cornell Clubs (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Cornell Penn luncheon (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Minutes Business Meeting, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Secondary Schools Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Financial, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Annual business meeting dinner, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Theatre Party, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Sympathy Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Letters from members, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Athletic events, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Gibson Island Party, 1958 and 1959 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Duplications of 1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- JAC (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Christmas Luncheon (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Copies of Correspondence with University, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Final annotated by-laws Rough, 12 May 1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Cornell Club by-laws preparatory (Box 2, Folder 48)
- From Cornell Club of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Meeting notices, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Cornell Clubs (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Club Manual, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Club Program Planning Section, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Correspondence with Milton E Hilliard Jr. (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Flatlist, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Working with the News (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Misc Book (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Activities (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cornell Club (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Secondary School (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Hilltod Theatre Party, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Flatlists, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ILR conference, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Cornell Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1966-May 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Misc Papers (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cornell Hilltop parties, 1955-1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Cornell Women's Club of Baltimore Merger Ballots (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nominating committee and reference list of members, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Annual Dinner, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Changes to Mailing Lists, Additions (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Secondary Schools, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Undergrad List, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Merger Ballots (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Scholarship (Box 3, Folder 18)
- General (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Financial (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Cornell List- Maryland, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Minutes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Women's Club (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Theatre Party, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- The Cayugan, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Master Copy Cornell Club By-Laws (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Cornell Women's Club of Baltimore, 1954-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Easton Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Cornell Club of Maryland Misc (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Cornell Alumni University, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
- SECY work CY, by-laws. Cornell Club of Maryland, May 29, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Cornell Club Press By-Laws, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Meeting Minutes, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Cornell Club, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- The Littlest Jones (Caroling Wood Young), 6 June (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Cornell Sec. Sch. Activities Historical Files (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Cornell College Nights (Box 3, Folder 37)
- House Improvement (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Cornell Special (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Green Box (1) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Annual reports and member lists
- Green Box files (2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Women's club information, event invitations
- Green Box files (3) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Flyers and scripts from events and speeches
- Green Box files (4) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Information on Cornell and finances
- Green Box (5) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Songs and prayers
- 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 1964-1968 binder (2) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Master Copies of Cornell Picnic Material, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Cornell Club of Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cornell in the News, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)